List data = [
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c0c",
    "correctAnswer": "Atlanta",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Dallas", "Houston", "Columbus"],
    "question": "Which city was burned by General Sherman in 1864?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950308",
    "correctAnswer": "1066",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1000", "1120", "1257"],
    "question":
        "William the Conqueror was crowned on Christmas day, but in what year?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950349",
    "correctAnswer": "Stanley Baldwin",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Anthony Eden", "Winston Churchill", "Bonar Law"],
    "question": "Who Was Prime Minister When King Edward VIII Abdicated?",
    "tags": ["leaders", "uk", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950341",
    "correctAnswer": "Anne Of Cleeves",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn",
      "Catherine Parr",
      "Catherine of Aragon"
    ],
    "question": "Who Was The 4th Wife Of Henry VIII?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518fb",
    "correctAnswer": "Botany Bay",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Florida", "Hong Kong", "The Bay of Biscay"],
    "question": "What Was Formerly Called Stingray Harbour?",
    "tags": ["previous_names", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950300",
    "correctAnswer": "Turkey",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Chicken", "Horse", "Pig"],
    "question":
        "Yorkshireman William Strickland is believed to have brought the first _______ to Britain from North America in 1526?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950317",
    "correctAnswer": "Lenin",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Marx", "Stalin", "Gorbachev"],
    "question": "Who was the ruler of the USSR from 1917-22?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950430",
    "correctAnswer": "Capricorn",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Gemini", "Aries", "Scorpio"],
    "question":
        "If You Were Born On Christmas Day What Star Sign Would You Be?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951bb8",
    "correctAnswer": "The Opium War",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Hong Kong War",
      "The Mandarin War",
      "The Boxer Rebellion"
    ],
    "question": "How was the 1839-42 Anglo-Chinese war better known ?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611f2c4b176d54800e3d46",
    "correctAnswer": "1949",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1941", "1970", "1923"],
    "question":
        "In which year did the communists come into to power in Beijing following the Chinese Civil War?",
    "tags": ["events", "revolutions", "wars", "cold_war", "politics", "china"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518c5",
    "correctAnswer": "Luddites",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Antitechs", "Weavos", "Resisters"],
    "question":
        "What Was The Name Given To Textile Workers Who Opposed Modernisation During The Nineteenth Century?",
    "tags": ["words", "1800's", "technology", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611f66014f58b5fc1a3fce",
    "correctAnswer": "2010",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["2016", "2004", "1998"],
    "question": "When did the Arab Spring topple a number of governments?",
    "tags": ["events", "revolutions", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611ff34b176d54800e3d7c",
    "correctAnswer": "2005",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["2001", "2009", "2013"],
    "question": "In which year was the first video uploaded to YouTube?",
    "tags": ["events", "firsts", "the_internet", "technology", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611fe94b176d54800e3d79",
    "correctAnswer": "1926",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1899", "1949", "1866"],
    "question": "When did Roald Amundsen first reach the North Pole?",
    "tags": ["events", "firsts", "exploration", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95039d",
    "correctAnswer": "The Stuarts",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["The Tudors", "The Plantagenets", "The Lancasters"],
    "question": "Which Royal House Ruled England Between 1603 & 1714?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503d8",
    "correctAnswer": "Melmac",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Barnzac", "Tonzac", "Fardac"],
    "question": "What planet was 'ALF' from?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95035f",
    "correctAnswer": "Lee Harvey Oswald",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["John F Kennedy", "John Lennon", "Ronald Reagan"],
    "question": "Who Was Shot Dead In Dallas On 24th November 1963?",
    "tags": ["history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517d8",
    "correctAnswer": "President Nassar",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "President Kassar",
      "President Passar",
      "President Hassar"
    ],
    "question":
        "Which Egyptian president ordered the seizure of the Suez Canal in 1956?",
    "tags": ["1950's", "bodies_of_water", "events", "politics", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951b02",
    "correctAnswer": "Memphis",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Knoxville", "Nashville", "Dallas"],
    "question": "In which US City was Martin Luther King assassinated in 1968?",
    "tags": ["people", "usa", "1960's", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611f9d4b176d54800e3d65",
    "correctAnswer": "1945",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1929", "1960", "1911"],
    "question": "When was the ENIAC, the first programmable computer, created?",
    "tags": ["events", "firsts", "technology", "inventions", "history"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  }
];
